sometimes when people order fries they
act like it's a little adventure maybe
like should we get a plate of fries for
the table should we do it should we
share some falls they're gonna make sure
that everyone's on board with it it's
like if I get fries you'll have a couple
right if I get fries to the table you I
know you left fries if I get fries
should we do it let's be bad come on
let's do it
all right we're gonna take a plate of
fries it's like a group of couples
agreeing to do ecstasy together thank
you I actually just quit drinking a
couple months ago because uh-oh I'm not
exactly slap happy about it myself but I
had a problem
because I was blacking out all the time
and I wasn't I talked to my doctor and
he said it's not that you drink too much
it's just that after a couple major
blackouts you black out easier and
easier after that so I would just have
like a couple drinks in my brain would
be like okay I see where this is headed
we're just gonna power down now and get
restarted sometime tomorrow morning the
morning the morning after a blackout
though is so strange because I always
feel like this detective trying to solve
the mystery of how I got home the night
before it's the case of the empty wallet
and the for some reason bleeding me and
luckily I can get right on the case
because I'm still fully clothed from the
night before
[Music]
he's always weird when I go out with
like some money and blackout and wake up
with no money it was a lot weirder when
I go out with some money blackout and
wake up with more money earned money
that men can I had traded goods and/or
services and blacked out it's not
anything wholesome it's not like I was
temping at a real-estate office so I
have this new phenomenon in my life
where like late at night on the street
women will see me as a threat that is
funny yeah that is silly
that is silly it's kind of flattering in
its own way but at the same time it's
weird because like I'm still afraid of
being kidnapped honestly but I'll give
you the best example of this a few
months ago I was at a subway station at
two o'clock in the morning all right and
at this station I'm changing trains and
you have to walk down this long hallway
in order to change trains so it's 2
o'clock in the morning it's just me and
this woman and we're walking along and
she's walking a few yards ahead of me
but she keeps giving me like like the
over the shoulder like that you know and
then she starts to pick up the pace she
starts to walk a lot faster so I think
oh she must hear the train coming
well you know maybe she feels it in her
feet like a Native American so I start
to I start to sprint down the hallway at
him
and she looks back and she's like and
then she gives chase right so now we're
booking it down the corridor at two
o'clock in the morning
and I'm gaining on her I'm gaining on
her and we're getting to the end of the
hallway and she starts to go into that
like dead-end shuffle you know that
women do when you chase him and I'm
almost at her I'm almost at her and then
it dawns on me
oh she's running from me because in her
eyes I'm an adult and adults rape each
other
so I wanted to go up to her and be like
hey whoa no no I'm not like I'm not like
a I'm not a man I'm some stupid Punk you
know but I think that that would be
equally creepy as if you were in a
subway station at two o'clock in the
morning and I chased you down grabbed
you and said I'm not gonna rape you I'm
a little boy years ago I was walking
down the street and a homeless guy came
up to me and he walked up to me and he
pushed me like that he pushed me in the
chest and then he said these things in
this order he pushed me and he said
excuse me
I am homeless I am gay I have AIDS new
in town
you're gonna close with new in town that
is not the most dramatic thing that you
just said as they say in the movie Jerry
Maguire you had me at AIDS here's how I
would have ordered those things I have
said excuse me I'm new in town and it
gets worse didn't that guy practice his
like pitch it all in the mirror that
morning and just figure out what he was
gonna say you know it's like in the
morning just be like all right what am I
gonna do today what am i doing all right
I'll walk up and say hello no just too
subtle pushing pushing and I'm gonna say
I'm new in town no no hold back hold
back saver
bill did that push it I go I have AIDS
no that's too strong
I will start with the fact that I am
homeless as that is the given then full
back story I will pepper in the fact
that I am gay which I know it's tough
for gay youths on the street but that's
not like a reason for money you can't be
like hey would you help me out I'm very
gay I'm like a few dollars I always
loved how we phrased it by the way he
didn't say I'm living on the street he
said I'm new in town like it was
intriguing like he wanted me to set him
up with somebody like I have a friend
who's like this no single guys left in
Manhattan and I'm like I know someone
who's new in town what are three other
things about him my girlfriend is a
Jewish woman which is I did on purpose
that's kind of creepy I don't mean like
I got one I mean like I I I'm not Jewish
but I've always really liked Jewish
people I just like them a lot and I
really like dating Jewish women they're
great because like I think a lot of
problems that people have in
relationships are with communication
because guys don't know what women are
thinking and with Jewish women you do
not have to guess what they're thinking
they will tell you my girlfriend's
wonderful though I listen to everything
my girlfriend says I don't mean she
bosses me around I just listened to
everything she says because before I had
a girlfriend I never had someone who's
always standing next to me who can just
point out obvious things that are
happening
like we'll be in a restaurant and my
girlfriend will be like you ordered your
food an hour ago it should be here by
now
and I'm like yeah it should it's like
having a lawyer for everyday life should
be like the bus driver shouldn't talk to
you that way and I'm like now he
shouldn't before I had a girlfriend I
had no standard for how I should be
treated as a human being you could do
anything to me I was just like a young
Motown singer
I was just shiny and dumb and easy to
trick give me a whole hundred dollars
for all of my songs where do I sign mr.
Barry Gordy and now when I'm not with my
girlfriend you can still do anything to
me I will tolerate any treatment like I
travel alone sometimes you know and I'll
put up with anything you know like I'll
book a ticket on some garbage airline
you know I don't want to name an actual
airline so let's just make one up let's
call it like Delta Airlines so I'll book
a ticket on Delta Airlines and I'll show
up at the airport then I go can I get on
the plane now please and they go now
it's delayed nine hours and I go okay
and I go to the bathroom and then I come
out of the bathroom and I go any updates
and they go yeah we took off while you
were in the bathroom because we hate you
I take this meal voucher that doesn't
work
go fetch and I go okay and I go over to
the Wolfgang Puck Express and I go can I
have a sandwich please and they go no
and I go okay and they go you're a
little fat girl aren't you and I go no
and they go say it and I go I'm a little
fat girl and then I go over to the Delta
helpdesk which is an oxymoron and I go
can I please go home on an airplane they
go no in fact we're gonna frame you for
murder you're gonna go to jail for 30
years and I go why are you doing this to
me and they go because we're Delta
Airlines and life is a nightmare
I'm sorry I was indisposed I'm sorry I'm
sorry I was indisposed
I am almost jinxed it out there because
I have a mic on and I had to pee I mean
I that's what going peeing with a
lavalier on is now called jinx in it and
I went into the bathroom and I was like
I don't know I was like this is so
ridiculous
you behave differently now in light of
the jinx I mean he always dressed it up
a little when you had a microphone on in
the bathroom but now you really have to
be worried so the only thing I did
differently because I peed regular and
stuff and I didn't talk to myself at all
but I washed my hands like loudly and
and traditionally with lather and
everything being like the sound guy must
think I'm the best
real quick before I get into anything
the nine thing about it the jinx is my
favorite show ever that I hope doesn't
win an Emmy because no for real cuz
who's gonna win the Emmy that Andrew
Jarecki and the HBO people I don't have
this much venom for him but all those
people are gonna get up there and get an
Emmy and who should get an Emmy our
little friend our dear friend Bobby the
jinx should win every Emmy that's ever
been invented he has been more this guy
is so good at being on TV
did you see the jinx did you see it
young girl did you see the jinx this guy
this guy this guy killed three people
and yet you'll watch it young lady and
you'll go I like this guy why do I like
this guy how old are you you're 13
perfect age you'll be sitting there and
you go look at me I'm 13 and I love this
guy
and I asked what's your name Lucy that's
great
so I I asked my wife I was like why do
people keep marrying the jinx and she
went oh I get it she said because he's
so confident and Lucy he is confidence
is the biggest currency we have you know
no no this is prepared material Lucy coz
think about it Lucy no one in the OJ
Simpson trial won an Emmy
from 94 to 95 there you didn't need to
watch any TV shows there's thing called
OJ Simpson trial and it was the it was
the best thing that ever happened on TV
ever is a murder trial sounds terrible
right it was so goddamn entertaining
these people delivered everyone in that
trial delivered they went up and they
went what's your name I'm Kato Kaelin
all right here's the ball on the tee and
a nadie would knock it out of the park
and there was a guy named Johnny Cochran
and this guy does not have an Emmy he's
dead
he died he died without an Emmy and this
was the most entertaining man you'd love
him Lucy this guy would put on a knit
cap and goof around with the murder
evidence either one of two things happen
and we truly don't know either Oh Jay
Simpson murdered his wife and then like
took off a glove and was like you know
did like throw it over his shoulder was
like done with that glove you hide of
that I do he threw away his glove or a
cop planted the glove both very
entertaining
so OJ had to try on the gloves in front
of the jury Lucy I know you all know
this I'm telling Lucy and he gets out
he's like oh these are my gloves and he
tries to put him on he goes he actually
bit his tongue go watch it it's on
YouTube I watched it recently keep going
right and then he goes like thanks very
much for listening to me my name is down
you're really fun thank you
[Music]